GitHub

I am a third-year Computer Science student at Bar-Ilan University, maintaining a GPA of 86, which reflects my unwavering commitment to academic excellence. I am highly self-motivated and dedicated to ensuring top-quality assurance for products. My expertise lies in a deep understanding of Computer Science fundamentals. I also excel in interpersonal and communication skills and am recognized for my creativity, initiative, and high productivity.



SKILLS

Languages - C, C++, Java, Python and JavaScript.

Web development technologies - HTML, CSS, React , Node.js, Express.js.

Database - MongoDB, SQLite.

<u>Courses</u> - Data Structures , Algorithms, Object-Oriented Programming, Computer Architecture, Computer Networks, Operating systems, Software Engineering.



EDUCATION

Computer science Student - Bar Ilan university (2021)

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science expected graduation date October 2024.
- excellence in Computational Complexity (99) and Advanced Programming (96).

Mikveh Israel High school (2009 – 2015)

Majored in biology and physics.



PROJECTS

WINK chat application (JavaScript, java)

- Cross-platform chat application, where we developed an efficient and scalable server using Node.js
 with Express framework. We utilized MongoDB as the database to store and retrieve data. The clientside was built using React, offering a responsive and user-friendly interface. real-time communication
 was implemented using Socket.IO.
- Additionally, we extended the application's reach to Android users by creating an Android app using
 Android Studio. The real-time communication for the app was facilitated through Firebase, while
 SQLite provided local storage for offline functionality.

Arkanoid (Java)

- Developed a Java implementation of the classic Arkanoid game.
- Utilized object-oriented programming (OOP) design patterns.

KNN classifier server (C++)

- Collaborated in a team to Implemented KNN algorithm in C++ for classification and regression tasks.
- Designed a TCP-based server that supports parallel connections from multiple clients, providing
 options to load data, modify algorithm parameters, perform classification, display results, and save
 data.



EXPERIENCE

Security officer | Israel Airports Authority (2019–2021)

A unit that aims to handle complicated security incidents and counterterrorism. High-level interpersonal relationship with executive security factors.

Combat medic | IDF (2016 – 2018)

Combat Medic at Givati Brigade.

Medical responsibility for a company both routinely and in emergencies.